

Gautier, MS 39553 6014025664 blake.bounds23@gmail.com

Mississippi Gulf Coast Community College student studying engineering, also studying for the CCNA exam. Talented Kitchen Manager experienced in monitoring inventory, team planning and building, and customer service. Trains and supervises kitchen personnel on proper preparation and cooking techniques. Schedules and performs repairs to kitchen equipment.

LINKS

https://www.linkedin.com/in/blake-bounds-566084230/

WORK EXPERIENCE

Kitchen Manager

11/2018 to 07/2021

Sonic Corp

Wiggins, MS

- Delegated food preparation duties down to cooks and followed up with cooks to verify proper preparation and production of meals
- Delivered in-depth training to workers in food preparation and customer-facing roles to promote strong team performance
- · Applied knowledge of previous supply needs and forecasted business levels to estimate required supplies
- · Identified team weak points and implemented corrective actions to resolve concerns.

Kitchen Manager

07/2021 to 12/2021

Sonic Corp

Gautier, MS

- Delegated food preparation duties down to cooks and followed up with cooks to verify proper preparation and production of meals
- Delivered in-depth training to workers in food preparation and customer-facing roles to promote strong team performance
- · Applied knowledge of previous supply needs and forecasted business levels to estimate required supplies

Identified team weak points and implemented corrective actions to resolve concerns.

SKILLS

Cisco routing and switching

Analytical Thinking

MS Office

C++ Programming

Team Leader

Customer service

EDUCATION

Mississippi Gulf Coast Community College

Associate
Engineering
Gautier, MS
08/2020 to Present

Supply ordering and management

Stone High School

High school or equivalent General Wiggins, MS 08/2016 to 05/2020

GROUPS

Key Club

- Raised money for charities and organizations
- Participated in organizational and leadership projects

AWARDS

CCNA 1

05/2019

- Stone High School
- Awarded to the top performer of the CCNA 1 class

Academic Excellence Award

08/2020

- Mississippi Gulf Coast Community College
- ACT score of 25